Guide to the Roy Edwin Ramseier Papers
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- Technical Drawings, 1935-1980; Series IV
  - Fernley, Nevada, 1964-1969 (Box 147 (Broadside))
  - Fernley, Nevada, 1964-1969 (Box 148 (Broadside))
  - Fernley, Nevada, 1964-1969 (Box 149 (Broadside))
  - Lovelock, Nevada, 1964-1966 (Box 150 (Broadside))
  - Lovelock, Nevada, 1964-1966 (Box 151 (Broadside))
  - Lovelock, Nevada, 1964-1966 (Box 152 (Broadside))
  - Lovelock, Nevada, 1964-1966 (Box 153 (Broadside))
  - Lovelock, Nevada, 1964-1966 (Box 154 (Broadside))
  - Lovelock, Nevada, 1964-1966 (Box 155 (Broadside))
  - Lovelock, Nevada, 1964-1966 (Box 156 (Broadside))
  - Lovelock, Nevada, 1964-1966 (Box 157 (Broadside))
  - Lovelock, Nevada, 1964-1966 (Box 158 (Broadside))
  - Lovelock, Nevada, 1964-1966 (Box 159 (Broadside))
  - Lovelock, Nevada, 1964-1966 (Box 160 (Broadisde))
  - Lovelock, Nevada, 1964-1966 (Box 161 (Broadside))
  - Lovelock, Nevada, 1964-1966 (Box 162 (Broadside))
  - Lovelock, Nevada, 1964-1966 (Box 163 (Broadside))
  - Lovelock, Nevada, 1964-1966 (Box 164 (Broadside))
  - Lovelock, Nevada, 1964-1966 (Box 165 (Broadside))
  - El Paso de Robles, California, 1947-1960 (Box 166 (Broadside))
  - El Paso de Robles, California, 1947-1960 (Box 167 (Broadside))
  - El Paso de Robles, California, 1947-1960 (Box 168 (Broadside))
  - El Paso de Robles, California, 1947-1960 (Box 169 (Broadside))
  - El Paso de Robles, California, 1947-1960 (Box 170 (Broadside))
  - El Paso de Robles, California, 1947-1960 (Box 171 (Broadside))
  - El Paso de Robles, California, 1947-1960 (Box 172 (Broadside))
  - Irvington, California, 1948 (Box 173 (Broadside))
  - Irvington, California, 1948 (Box 174 (Broadside))
  - Irvington, California, 1948 (Box 175 (Broadside))
  - Irvington, California, 1948 (Box 176 (Broadside))
  - Irvington, California, 1948 (Box 177 (Broadside))
  - Irvington, California, 1948 (Box 178 (Broadside))
  - Irvington, California, 1948 (Box 179 (Broadside))
  - Niles, California Sanitary District, 1946 (Box 180 (Broadside))
  - Pleasanton, California, 1949-1950 (Box 181 (Broadside))
  - Pleasanton, California, 1949-1950 (Box 182 (Broadside))
  - Pleasanton, California, 1949-1950 (Box 183 (Broadside))
  - Pleasanton, California, 1949-1950 (Box 184 (Broadside))
  - Pleasanton, California, 1949-1950 (Box 185 (Broadside))
  - Pleasanton, California, 1949-1950 (Box 186 (Broadside))
  - Pleasanton, California, 1949-1950 (Box 187 (Broadside))
  - Pleasanton, California, 1949-1950 (Box 188 (Broadside))
  - Pleasanton, California, 1949-1950 (Box 189 (Broadside))
  - San Miguel, California, undated (Box 190 (Broadside))
  - San Miguel, California, undated (Box 191 (Broadside))
  - Yreka, California, 1952 (Box 192 (Broadside))
  - Yreka, California, 1952 (Box 193 (Broadside))
  - Meadowood, 1962-1972 (Box 194 (Broadside))
  - Meadowood, 1962-1972 (Box 195 (Broadside))
  - Meadowood, 1962-1972 (Box 196 (Broadside))
  - Meadowood, 1962-1972 (Box 197 (Broadside))
  - Meadowood, 1962-1972 (Box 198 (Broadside))
  - Meadowood, 1962-1972 (Box 199 (Broadside))
  - Meadowood, 1962-1972 (Box 200 (Broadside))
  - Meadowood, 1962-1972 (Box 201 (Broadside))
  - Contra Loma Regional Park, 1980 (Box 202 (Broadside))
  - Installation Diagrams, undated (Box 203 (Broadside))
  - Installation Diagrams, undated (Box 204 (Broadside))
  - Installation Diagrams, undated (Box 205 (Broadside))
  - Berryessa, 1964 (Box 206 (Broadside))
  - Berryessa, 1964 (Box 207 (Broadside))
  - Berryessa, 1964 (Box 208 (Broadside))
  - Dunsmuir, California, 1949 (Box 209 (Broadside))
  - Mokelumne Hill, 1949 (Box 210 (Broadside))
  - Pla-Vada, 1957-1958 (Box 211 (Broadside))
  - Pla-Vada, 1957-1958 (Box 212 (Broadside))
  - Pla-Vada, 1957-1958 (Box 213 (Broadside))
  - Pla-Vada, 1957-1958 (Box 214 (Broadside))
  - San Andreas, 1954-1958 (Box 215 (Broadside))
  - San Andreas, 1954-1958 (Box 216 (Broadside))
  - Tahoe Pines, 1964 (Box 217 (Broadside))
  - Tahoe Pines, 1964 (Box 218 (Broadside))
  - Anthony Chabot Regional Park, 1971 (Box 219 (Broadside))
  - Anthony Chabot Regional Park, 1971 (Box 220 (Broadside))
  - Anthony Chabot Regional Park, 1971 (Box 221 (Broadside))
  - Anthony Chabot Regional Park, 1971 (Box 222 (Broadside))
  - Anthony Chabot Regional Park, 1971 (Box 223 (Broadside))
  - Anthony Chabot Regional Park, 1971 (Box 224 (Broadside))
  - Anthony Chabot Regional Park, 1971 (Box 225 (Broadside))
  - Anthony Chabot Regional Park, 1971 (Box 226 (Broadside))
  - Anthony Chabot Regional Park, 1971 (Box 227 (Broadside))
  - Anthony Chabot Regional Park, 1971 (Box 228 (Broadside))
  - Anthony Chabot Regional Park, 1971 (Box 229 (Broadside))
  - Anthony Chabot Regional Park, 1971 (Box 230 (Broadside))
  - Don Castro Regional Park, 1967 (Box 231 (Broadside))
  - Thomas Roberts Recreational Area, 1973 (Box 232 (Broadside))
  - Alameda Beach, 1968 (Box 233 (Broadside))
  - Alameda Beach, 1968 (Box 234 (Broadside))
  - Tahoe Lakeside, 1967 (Box 235 (Broadside))
  - Tamarack Mutual Water Company, 1970 (Box 236 (Broadside))
  - White Sulphur Springs, 1968 (Box 237 (Broadside))
  - Standard Drawings, 1965-1967 (Box 238 (Broadside))
  - Standard Drawings, 1965-1967 (Box 239 (Broadside))
  - Castle Rock County, 1955 (Box 240 (Broadside))
  - Castle Rock County, 1955 (Box 241 (Broadside))
  - Castle Rock County, 1955 (Box 242 (Broadside))
  - Castle Rock County, 1955 (Box 243 (Broadside))
  - Albany, California, 1960 (Box 244 (Broadside))
  - Castlewood Country Club, 1964-1972 (Box 245 (Broadside))
  - Martinez, California, 1971 (Box 246 (Broadside))
  - Lincoln Valley Ranch, 1968 (Box 247 (Broadside))
  - Djerassi Residence, 1970 (Box 248 (Broadside))
  - Southern Public Utility District, 1951 (Box 249 (Broadside))
  - Gregory Gardens, 1952-1953 (Box 250 (Broadside))
  - Gregory Gardens, 1952-1953 (Box 251 (Broadside))
  - Gregory Gardens, 1952-1953 (Box 252 (Broadside))
  - Gregory Gardens, 1952-1953 (Box 253 (Broadside))
  - Gregory Gardens, 1952-1953 (Box 254 (Broadside))
  - Gregory Gardens, 1952-1953 (Box 255 (Broadside))
  - Gregory Gardens, 1952-1953 (Box 256 (Broadside))
  - Gregory Gardens, 1952-1953 (Box 257 (Broadside))
  - Diablo Valley College, 1969-1970 (Box 258 (Broadside))
  - Diablo Valley College, 1969-1970 (Box 259 (Broadside))
  - Diablo Valley College, 1969-1970 (Box 260 (Broadside))
  - Diablo Valley College, 1969-1970 (Box 261 (Broadside))
  - Unidentified project, undated (Box 262 (Broadside))